[{"answer": "Yeah", "docId": "Win-Win.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "I love you too, sweetie. Bye", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Well if that Judge deems you incapacitated then you will need a guardian. And if we can't find your daughter then the state..", "docId": "Win-Win.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "OK but if we can't find her then the State will have to become your guardian", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Who's the state", "docId": "Win-Win.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "That's crazy. I don't need that place's help. I got Jolie now. And there's no funny business between us so you know", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "How's the team doing", "docId": "Win-Win.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "What the hell happened? We used to be good", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Couple of months. The doctor says it's stress", "docId": "Win-Win.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Yeah. Jogging. Why the hell you think I'm doing this", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "I know. But I need you to stay in this new place for a while. It's nice. You'll like it", "docId": "Win-Win.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Yeah, that's what he said", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Yeah", "docId": "Win-Win.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Where does he live", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Yeah. You should go outside", "docId": "Win-Win.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Good night, my friend", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "OK. my friend", "docId": "Win-Win.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "No. I'm going home", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "It's embarrassing, guys", "docId": "Win-Win.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "I'm not getting paid enough", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "I'm not getting paid enough", "docId": "Win-Win.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "I care", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "I'm not enrolling him. He's just here until we reach his mother and figure this out", "docId": "Win-Win.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "I'm not just helping out the old man, my friend. It's not like it's charity work. I'm getting paid for it", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "We're trying to figure out where he can wrestle", "docId": "Win-Win.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "No. Not right", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "I don't know why we didn't quit. Just the smell of that room brought back the memories. I hated it, it was like a form of sel", "docId": "Win-Win.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "my friend was average. I sucked. Sorry my friend", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Hey Vig, which kid is yours anyway", "docId": "Win-Win.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Really? You're son quit", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Yeah. But I never believe her anyway", "docId": "Win-Win.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "But this place is pretty nice", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Yeah. Let's go to my park", "docId": "Win-Win.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Yeah. My park", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Oh my God", "docId": "Win-Win.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Yeah. It was stupid. You could have killed yourself", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "I don't know. I guess it just feels like I'm in control. Of everything. You know what I mean", "docId": "Win-Win.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "It is", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "my friend, can you go get my friend for us", "docId": "Win-Win.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "He left? What do you mean", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "He left", "docId": "Win-Win.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "He left out the window", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "Yeah. She just told me today", "docId": "Win-Win.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "I don't know my friend. It's complicated", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "That scumbag! He never cared about anyone but himself and his fucking money. Did you know about this", "docId": "Win-Win.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "Please what", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "I want that commission! That should be mine", "docId": "Win-Win.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "Isn't that why you did it", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "You moved an old man out of his house to make money? Have you lost your freaking mind", "docId": "Win-Win.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "Really? Or you just didn't think you'd get caught", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "No. We got in a fight because he's an asshole", "docId": "Win-Win.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "Yeah, really, Stem", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "Oak Knoll.  You're right, that's not who I am", "docId": "Win-Win.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "I have to go court", "qsentId": 54}, {"answer": "Hi guys", "docId": "Win-Win.txt", "asentId": 57, "question": "Dude, I'm your assistant coach. And just notice who isn't here", "qsentId": 56}]